getweblist.com 2012-10-04

# GetWebList: Privacy Policy

Nothing is more important to GetWebList.com than protecting the private information of visitors to our site. Below you'll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your and your children's personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, email address, telephone number and/or other identifying information) and preserving the integrity of the medium.

Please read the following carefully. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email.

### Gathering and Use of Information

GetWebList.com will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third party without first receiving the user's permission. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

Visitors to the GetWebList.com Web Site may voluntarily supply certain personally identifiable information in connection with (i)contest or sweepstakes registration, (ii) subscription registration for sites or services which require subscription (such as email newsletters), (iii) requests for membership information and (iv) e-commerce transactions. In addition, personally identifiable information is voluntarily provided in connection with certain content submissions, community postings (i.e., forums or bulletin boards), comments and suggestions, or voting.

GetWebList.com may use such information only for conducting the activities stated above, for internal marketing and promotional purposes, or, on occasion, when mailing lists are made available to other organizations. (The occasional provision of mailing lists to such organizations is the only case where such information would be provided to third parties). For more information regarding GetWebList.com's policies on the handling and use of GetWebList.com's membership list, please see GetWebList.com's Membership List Policy. The extent of such use is always explained at the time a site visitor provides such information. If the visitor does not want this information collected and used by us for the disclosed internal purposes, the visitor is given an opportunity to 'opt-out.' Our visitors need to recognize, however, that under certain circumstances, if they select to 'opt-out' they may not be eligible for certain activities for which the personally identifiable information is needed. (For example, if a contest participant elects to 'opt-out' on permitting us to collect and use their personal information, we cannot contact them if they win without using such information.)

### Acceptance of these GetWebList.com Web Site Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this GetWebList.com Web Site Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the GetWebList.com Web Site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please email.
